export const FamilyQuestions = [
  {
    category: "Family",
    question:
      "John's wife attended which school for her fully subsidized Master's degree?",
    options: ["UVa", "Dartmouth", "Yale", "Harvard"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question: "Which specialty dish includes marshmallows?",
    options: [
      "Holiday Salad",
      "Len's Peanut Butter Pie",
      "Jude Potatoes",
      "Mom's Ecclair",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    category: "Jaje",
    question: "What's the proper spelling of the sausage Dobie used to make?",
    options: ["Kibassi", "Kielbasa", "Cibasi", "Kabassi"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    category: "Jaje",
    question: "Where was Jaje born?",
    options: [
      "Avoka, PA",
      "Phildelphia, PA",
      "Tunkhannock, PA",
      "Pittsburgh, PA",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question: "Who has Jude NOT taken into the basement?",
    options: ["Lauren", "Hajira", "Sophie", "Avery"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question: "What was Jake's Regina's last name?",
    options: ["Porter", "Chaillo", "Mariosa", "Corolla"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question: "Who did Suri HATE?",
    options: ["Mom", "Noah", "Jake", "Jude"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question:
      "Which of Jude's friends is most likely to end up on the cover of TMZ?",
    options: ["Colton", "Logan", "James", "John"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question:
      "What did Mom think Jude was REALLY into during elementary school?",
    options: ["Sex", "Parkour", "Dancing", "Transgender People"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question: "Jude is said to resemble which fast food icon?",
    options: [
      "Ronald McDonald",
      "Dennis The Menace",
      "Colonel Sanders",
      "Grimace",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question:
      "Which weapon have four (and possibly more) of Jude's friends used on his bare ass?",
    options: ["Nerf Gun", "Bow and Arrow", "Ribbed Dildo", "Sword"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question: "How many teeth did Jonah have pulled in Eighth Grade?",
    options: ["10", "9", "8", "7"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question:
      "What weight did Jonah need to cut to to qualify for McGrath's team when he was 11?",
    options: ["85", "72", "75", "82"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question: "In which class was Jonah caught up in a cheating scandal?",
    options: ["History", "Biology", "Math", "Chemistry"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question:
      "What was the name of the rollercoaster Jonah wanted to get off of at his first trip to six flags?",
    options: ["Thunder", "Goliath", "Cyclone", "El Toro"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question:
      "What was the name of the roller coaster Jonah wanted to get off of at his first trip to six flags?",
    options: ["Thunder", "Goliath", "Cyclone", "El Toro"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    category: "Family",
    question: "Which water slide did you push Noah down against his will?",
    options: ["Mammoth", "River Canyon", "Summit Plummet", "Everest"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
];
